Finding Aid for Office of Financial Aid (University of Michigan) records, 1954-2000 (bulk 1977-1996)
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
Office of Financial Aid (University of Michigan) records 1954-2000 1977-1996
University of Michigan. Office of Financial Aid.
03120 Bimu 2
The Office of Financial Aid at the University of Michigan administers need- and merit-based financial support programs for students. The records include topical files detailing the operations of the office, its interactions with other university units and groups, and outside activities, as well as federal funding reports and applications and information on alumni scholarships.
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
10.25 linear feet
The record group (donor. no. 8672 ) was received in several accessions beginning in 1997.
The record group is open without restriction.
The Office of Financial Aid at the University of Michigan administers need- and merit-based financial support programs for students. While provision of financial support to students began very early in the history of the university, it was not until 1962 that a discrete financial aid office was established, as part of a new, comprehensive administrative structure for student affairs that replaced the Dean of Men and Dean of Women. Walter Rea, previously Dean of Men, was named Director of Student Financial Aids that year, in addition to serving as assistant to the vice president of student affairs.
In 1968-69, the office and its operations were reorganized to reflect the increased need for centralized record keeping and computerization. The policy of packaging aid, developing an individualized program of loans, grants and work for each student, was introduced at that time, as was the College Work-Study program. Ronald Brown led the reorganization effort and was named director in January 1969 when Rea retired. The office was moved within the organizational structure of the university as well, reporting to the Vice President for Academic Affairs rather than the Vice President for Student Affairs. Prior to the early 1970s, the office was referred to as the Office of Financial Aids or the Office of Student Financial Aid, until settling on its current name around 1972.
The operations of the Office of Financial Aid have become increasingly complex in the years since. The Office of Financial Aid coordinates and administers the university's participation in three major federal government aid programs: Perkins Loans, College Work-Study, and the Federal Supplemental Education Opportunity Grant (FSEOG) program. The office is also responsible for many need- and merit-based scholarships, loans, and grants for undergraduate students. For graduate students, the office administers federal loan and work-study programs only. Most of the graduate schools and colleges have student support offices that administer scholarships and aid programs designed specifically for their own students.
For current information on the Office of Financial Aid and its programs, consult their website at: http://www.finaid.umich.edu/.
Directors of Financial Aid
1962-1968 Walter Rea (Assistant to the Vice President and Director of Student Financial Aids)
1969-1971 Ronald Brown
1971-1977 Tom Butts
1977-1995 Harvey Grotrian
1995-1997 Judith Harper (interim)
1997- Pamela Fowler
The University of Michigan Office of Financial Aid record group consists of five series: Office of Financial Aid, University of Michigan, Outside Activities, Federal Funding Reports and Applications and Alumni Scholarships. Several accessions were brought together at the time of processing. The files include material mainly from three directors of the office, Tom Butts, Harvey Grotrian, and Judith Harper, as well as from several subordinate departments and staff. A small amount of older material from a predecessor office, the Office of Scholarships (which reported to the Dean of Men), is also included.
Subjects:
University of Michigan. Office of Financial Aid.; Student aid--Michigan.; University of Michigan--Funds and scholarships.; University of Michigan--Students--Scholarships, fellowships, etc.; Butts, Thomas A.
- Office of Financial Aid 1954-1999
  The Office of Financial Aid series, 1954-1999 (5.5 linear feet), contains topical files that include information about the policies, procedures, and operations of the office and its departments. The policy files are particularly useful, as they detail the development and implementation of various policies and programs. The series also includes a small amount of historical information about the Office of Scholarships, a predecessor to the Office of Financial Aid.
  - Accomplishments 1990-1996 (Box 1)
  - Audit
    - General 1977-1982 (Box 1)
    - Federal Audit 1986 (Box 1)
    - Flint 1986 (Box 1)
    - Health Professions and Nursing Student Loan and Scholarship Programs 1977 (Box 1)
    - Internal Audit 1977-1985 (Box 1)
    - Internal Audit Reports 1968-1980 (Box 1)
    - Michigan Guaranteed Student Loan Program 1986-1987 (Box 1)
    - Operational Audit 1979-1980 (Box 1)
    - Opportunity Grant Program 1980 (Box 1)
    - Price Waterhouse 1984 (Box 1)
    - Program Review
      - 1983-1986 (Box 1)
      - 1995-1996 (Box 1)
    - State Audit 1979-1980 (Box 1)
  - Budget
    - Cost Containment 1993 (Box 1)
    - Financial Aid Model (from Office of Financial Analysis) 1982 (Box 1)
    - Financial Reports
      - End-of-Year Reports 1982-1996 (Box 1)
      - Projected Expenditures 1990-1997 (Box 1)
      - Spring/Summer Awards 1990-1996 (Box 1)
    - General Fund Request 1993-1997 (Box 1)
    - Operating Budget 1992-1993 (Box 1)
    - Parameters/Packages
      - 1982-1983 (Box 1)
      - 1993 (Box 1)
  - Departments
    - College Work-Study 1980-1983 (Box 1)
    - Counseling and Processing
      - General 1994-1997 (Box 1)
      - Counseling Services 1985-1986 (Box 1)
      - Intake Counseling 1976 (Box 1)
      - Peer Counseling 1979 (Box 1)
      - Processing 1985 (Box 1)
    - Director
      - Athletic Appeals 1986-1994 (Box 1)
      - Case Committee/Director Appeals 1984 (Box 1)
      - General Correspondence
        - 1983 (Box 1)
        - 1993-1996 (Box 1)
      - Management By Objective 1976-1978 (Box 1)
      - Management Report 1979 (Box 1)
      - Robert S. Holbrook 1982 (Box 1)
      - Strategic Planning 1992 (Box 1)
      - Survey of Directors of Aid and Presidents 1980 (Box 1)
    - Information Dissemination 1981 (Box 1)
    - Loans, Guaranteed Student Loans
      - Civil Liberties Loan Fund 1984 (Box 1)
      - Correspondence 1980-1986 (Box 1)
      - Default Rates 1996 (Box 1)
      - Federally Insured Student Loans 1973-1977, 3 folders (Box 1)
      - Guaranteed Loan Legislation 1971-1977 (Box 1)
      - Harvard Parent Loan Program 1976-1977 (Box 1)
      - HEAL 1978-1985 (Box 1)
      - Loan Collection Systems 1986-1987 (Box 1)
      - Long-Term University Loan Program 1983-1984 (Box 2)
      - National Direct Student Loan Program 1984 (Box 2)
      - PLUS 1980-1985 (Box 2)
      - Sallie Mae Options 1983 (Box 2)
      - Special Programs and Services Unit 1996 (Box 2)
      - Supplemental Loan Program 1982-1985 (Box 2)
    - Operations
      - Computer Packaging 1977-1981 (Box 2)
      - Computer Systems
        - General 1976-1978 (Box 2)
        - Development 1971-1986 (Box 2)
    - Scholarships
      - General 1982-1985 (Box 2)
      - Alumni Merit Scholarship Committee 1983-1988 (Box 2)
      - Athletics 1979-1985 (Box 2)
      - Bentley Scholarship 1983-1999 (includes photos) (Box 2)
      - Bill Knapp's Founders Scholars 1981-1987 (Box 2)
      - Burroughs Corporation Scholarship 1973 (includes photo) (Box 2)
      - Douglas McGreeham and Edward Siwik Scholarships 1982-1983 (Box 2)
      - Ford Motor Company Scholarship 1989 (Box 2)
      - General Motors Opportunity Scholarship 1984 (Box 2)
      - Graduate/Professional Programs 1981-1983 (Box 2)
      - Hallissey Scholarship 1987 (Box 2)
      - Isabel Quail Scholarship 1977 (Box 2)
      - Javits Fellowship 1988-1989 (Box 2)
      - Martin Luther King-Rosa Parks Fellowships 1986 (Box 2)
      - Merit
        - General 1983-1985 (Box 2)
        - Alumni Initiatives 1982 (Box 2)
        - Programs 1979-1985 (Box 2)
        - Recommendations 1983 (Box 2)
        - Studies 1976-1984 (Box 2)
      - Ralph G. Conger Scholarship 1965-1981 (Box 2)
      - ROTC 1985 (Box 2)
      - Seth Harrison Scholarship 1987 (Box 2)
      - Ufer Memorial Scholarship Fund 1982-1988 (Box 2)
      - University of Michigan Club of Greater Philadelphia 1986 (Box 2)
      - Wade H. McCree, Jr. Incentive Scholarship Program 1987 (Box 2)
  - Objectives 1982-1995 (Box 2)
  - Office of Scholarships (predecessor to Office of Financial Aid) 1954-1962 (Box 2)
  - Planning Seminars
    - 1977-1979 (Box 2)
    - 1980-1981 (Box 2)
    - 1983-1984 (Box 2)
    - 1985-1988 (Box 2)
    - 1989 (Box 2)
    - 1990 (Box 2)
  - Policies
    - Academic Progress 1976-1983 (Box 3)
    - Appeal Procedures
      - 1979 (Box 3)
      - 1990-1991 (Box 3)
    - Attrition/Retention 1981-1982 (Box 3)
    - Bridge Program 1994-1997 (Box 3)
    - Child Care Subsidy Program 1996-1997 (Box 3)
    - Citizenship Status Verification 1984 (Box 3)
    - Civil Liberties Loan Fund 1983-1984 (Box 3)
    - Defaults 1988 (Box 3)
    - Disabled Students 1986 (Box 3)
    - Draft Registration
      - General 1982-1983, 2 folders (Box 3)
      - Key Correspondence 1983 (Box 3)
      - Regents 1983 (Box 3)
    - Emergency Student Loans to Graduate Teaching Assistants 1983-1988 (Box 3)
    - Family Educational Rights and Privacy Act (FERPA) 1978-1983 (Box 3)
    - Federal Student Aid Allocations 1992-1996 (Box 3)
    - File Storage 1979-1980 (Box 3)
    - Health Professions Programs 1996-1997 (Box 3)
    - Independent Students 1983 (Box 3)
    - International Student Issues 1978-1995 (Box 3)
    - Jamaican Loan Scheme 1972-1974 (Box 3)
    - MCard 1995 (Box 3)
    - Michigan Incentive Grant 1987-1988 (Box 3)
    - Minority Graduate Student Scholarships 1980 (Box 3)
    - Minority Student Issues 1982-1987, 2 folders (Box 3)
    - Minority Students
      - General 1972-1989 (Box 3)
      - Enrollment 1973-1984 (Box 3)
      - Hispanic 1978-1982 (Box 3)
      - Incremental Costs 1985 (Box 3)
      - Merit Awards 1984 (Box 3)
      - Michigan Achievement 1982-1996 (Box 3)
      - Recruitment and Retention 1982-1986 (Box 3)
    - Mission Statement 1989 (Box 3)
    - National Graduate Fellows Program 1984-1985 (Box 3)
    - National Merit and Achievement 1976-1989, 2 folders (Box 3)
    - Native Americans
      - 1973-1992, 2 folders (Box 3)
      - 1995-1997 (includes American Indian Grant) (Box 3)
    - Notification
      - 1979-1983 (Box 4)
      - 1988-1996 (Box 4)
      - Resource and Aid Planner 1994-1996 (Box 4)
    - Opportunity Students
      - General 1971-1983, 2 folders (Box 4)
      - College Work-Study 1978-1979 (Box 4)
      - Meetings 1980 (Box 4)
      - Opportunity Program Coordinating Committee 1980-1982 (Box 4)
      - Packaging 1978-1980 (Box 4)
      - Program Proposal 1978-1979 (Box 4)
    - Outside Gift Aid 1982 (Box 4)
    - Packaging
      - 1972-1981 (Box 4)
      - 1988-1989 (Box 4)
      - 1994-1996 (Box 4)
      - Surveys 1983-1996 (Box 4)
    - Parental Contribution 1985 (Box 4)
    - Part-Time Students 1976-1980 (Box 4)
    - Policy Manual
      - 1982-1984, 2 folders (Box 4)
      - 1992-1994 (Box 4)
    - Professional Judgment
      - 1988 (Box 4)
      - 1996 (Box 4)
    - Public Service Intern Program 1975-1994 (Box 4)
    - Retention/Graduation 1990 (Box 4)
    - Salaried Grads 1979-1983, 2 folders (Box 4)
    - Satisfactory Progress 1981-1986 (Box 4)
    - Spring/Summer Responses 1981 (Box 4)
    - Social Security 1982 (Box 4)
    - Student Budgets
      - General 1976-1987 (Box 4)
      - Correspondence 1974-1983 (Box 4)
    - Student Deaths 1992 (Box 4)
    - Study Abroad 1971-1994, 2 folders (Box 5)
    - Truth in Lending 1974-1983 (Box 5)
    - Vietnamese Refugees 1975-1976 (Box 5)
    - Vocational Rehabilitation 1972-1975 (Box 5)
    - Miscellaneous 1982 (Box 5)
  - Procedures
    - Michigan Alternative Loan Program (MI-LOAN) 1996 (Box 5)
    - Michigan Competitive Scholarship 1985 (Box 5)
    - Pell Grant 1983-1986 (Box 5)
    - Registration
      - 1973-1980 (Box 5)
      - 1981-1986 (Box 5)
      - 1990-1997, 2 folders (Box 5)
    - Special Loans 1985 (Box 5)
    - Terms of Agreement, Department of Health, Education and Welfare (HEW) 1973-1985 (Box 5)
    - Title IX 1974-1976 (Box 5)
    - University Loan 1971-1981 (Box 5)
  - Services
    - Peer Counseling 1980-1984 (Box 5)
    - Publications
      - Minority Brochure 1985 (Box 5)
    - Service Concept 1992 (Box 5)
    - Service Hours 1992 (Box 5)
    - Service Leaflet 1990 (Box 5)
  - State Programs
    - American Indian Tuition Waiver 1995-1996 (Box 5)
    - Early Awareness 1995 (Box 5)
    - Michigan Educational Trust 1997 (Box 5)
    - Michigan Veterans Trust 1995-1997 (Box 5)
    - Survivors Tuition Waiver Program 1996 (Box 5)
  - Surveys and Questionnaires 1981-1984 (Box 5)
  - Task Forces and Studies
    - Alternative Financing Survey 1984-1986 (Box 5)
    - Budget Survey
      - 1974-1975
        - General (Box 5)
        - Student Comments (Box 5)
      - 1979-1981 (Box 5)
      - 1982-1983 (Box 5)
      - 1983-1987 (Box 5)
    - Debt Study 1986-1991 (Box 6)
    - Department of Education Experimental Sites Program 1995-1996 (Box 6)
    - Early Notification Project 1994-1995 (Box 6)
    - Enrollment Decision Project 1983-1984 (Box 6)
    - Institutional Survey 1983-1984, 2 folders (Box 6)
    - Minority Participation in Study Abroad Programs 1970-1972 (Box 6)
    - Office of Financial Analysis Study 1982 (Box 6)
    - Reauthorization of Higher Education Act Impact Assessment 1992-1993 (Box 6)
    - SOFA 1992-1993 (Box 6)
    - 1040 Study, 1985 (Box 6)
    - Unmet Need by Academic Qualifications 1992 (Box 6)
    - Unmet Need Studies 1988 (Box 6)
- University of Michigan 1957-1994
  The University of Michigan series, 1957-1994 (2 linear feet), documents the Office of Financial Aid’s interactions and collaboration with other university units. The series includes information on a number of university committees related to financial aid, as well as correspondence with individual schools and colleges. Of particular relevance to the record group is material from the Financial Aid Advisory Committee.
  - Administration
    - Richard English 1977-1980 (Box 6)
    - Billy E. Frye 1981 (Box 6)
    - Alfred Sussman 1979-1980 (Box 6)
    - Mary Ann Swain 1992 (Box 6)
    - Frank Williams 1990 (Box 6)
  - Data Systems
    - Student Aid Management (SAM) 1976 (Box 6)
    - Student Aid Payment Database 1975 (Box 6)
  - Departments
    - Admissions
      - General 1973-1988 (Box 6)
      - Detroit Public Schools 1985-1987 (Box 6)
      - Notification 1982-1983 (Box 6)
      - Presentations 1981-1982 (Box 6)
    - Alumni 1982 (Box 6)
    - Alumni Association 1976-1988 (Box 6)
    - Athletic Department 1987 (Box 6)
    - Center for the Continuing Education of Women 1971-1987 (Box 6)
    - Coalition on the Use of Learning Skills (CULS) 1976-1983 (Box 6)
    - Development/University Relations 1982-1985 (Box 6)
    - Extension Service 1977-1986 (Box 6)
    - Housing Office 1975-1990 (Box 6)
    - Information Technology
      - Computer User Fee 1985-1986 (Box 6)
      - Engineering Computer User Fee 1983-1985 (Box 6)
    - Loan Collections 1976-1978 (Box 6)
    - Orientation 1973-1986 (Box 6)
    - Registrar 1977-1986 (Box 6)
    - University Information Systems 1993 (Box 6)
  - Groups
    - Academic Affairs Advisory Council (AAAC)-Presentation 1978 (Box 6)
    - Academic Records Project 1988 (Box 6)
    - Academic Services Board
      - General 1981-1983 (Box 6)
      - Academic Hold Credit 1977 (Box 6)
    - Admissions/Financial Aid Council 1978 (Box 6)
    - Budget Priorities Committee
      - General 1985 (Box 7)
      - Subcommittee on Student Financial Aid 1979-1980 (Box 7)
    - Commission on Minority Groups 1972 (Box 7)
    - Disaster Planning Group 1972 (Box 7)
    - Federal Legislative Action Group (FLAG) 1981-1982 (Box 7)
    - Financial Aid Advisory Committee
      - 1978-1985 (Box 7)
      - 1985-1991 (Box 7)
      - Background 1969-1985 (Box 7)
      - Merit Program Reports and Recommendations 1985-1987 (Box 7)
      - Minutes and Agendas 1985-1989 (Box 7)
    - Fiscal Planning Group
      - 1981 (Box 7)
      - 1982 (Box 7)
      - 1983-1984 (Box 7)
      - 1985 (Box 7)
      - 1988-1991 (Box 7)
    - Five Office 1977-1983 (Box 7)
    - Graduate Student Aid Task Force 1981-1986, 2 folders (Box 7)
    - Hold Credit Committee 1983 (Box 7)
    - Institutional Quality Control Project 1987-1989 (Box 7)
    - LS&A Admissions Team 1988-1989 (Box 7)
    - Michigan Annual Giving Committee 1984 (Box 7)
    - Michigan Student Assembly 1980-1982 (Box 7)
    - Permanent Committee on Scholarship 1957 (Box 7)
    - Student Data Systems Task Force 1978 (Box 7)
    - Undergraduate Admissions Advisory Committee 1988-1988 (Box 7)
    - Undergraduate Student Aid Task Force 1984 (Box 7)
    - University Merit Scholarship Coordinating Committee 1989 (Box 7)
  - Regents
    - General 1978-1982 (Box 7)
    - Cutler Report 1967 (Box 7)
    - Report
      - 1974-1976 (Box 7)
      - 1977 (Box 7)
      - 1979-1980 (Box 8)
      - 1981-1982 (Box 8)
    - Retreat 1975 (Box 8)
  - Schools and Colleges
    - Academic Unit Award Coordination 1980-1981 (Box 8)
    - Appeal Procedures 1990-1991 (Box 8)
    - Architecture and Urban Planning 1976-1989 (Box 8)
    - Business Administration 1981-1992 (Box 8)
    - Dental School
      - 1977-1992 (Box 8)
      - 1995 (Box 8)
    - Education 1976-1988 (Box 8)
    - Engineering 1981-1984 (Box 8)
    - Flint/Dearborn 1978-1984 (Box 8)
    - Law 1977-1985 (Box 8)
    - Library Science 1985 (Box 8)
    - LS&A
      - General 1975-1980 (Box 8)
      - Blue Ribbon Commission 1983-1986 (Box 8)
      - Scholarship Program Proposal 1986 (Box 8)
      - Undergraduate Research Opportunity Program (UROP) 1992 (Box 8)
    - Medical School 1974-1990 (Box 8)
    - Music
      - General 1979-1993 (Box 8)
      - Instrument Purchase 1978 (Box 8)
    - Natural Resources 1973-1985 (Box 8)
    - Nursing 1981-1989 (Box 8)
    - Pharmacy 1980-1989 (Box 8)
    - Public Health 1978-1984 (Box 8)
    - Rackham
      - 1975-1989 (Box 8)
      - 1996 (Box 8)
    - Residential College 1978 (Box 8)
    - School and College Report 1992-1994 (Box 8)
    - Social Work 1972-1983 (Box 8)
- Outside Activities 1974-1994
  The Outside Activities series, 1974-1994 (0.5 linear feet), includes information on the office's participation and cooperation with groups and initiatives outside the University of Michigan. Most of the series relates to state-level organizations and projects, though a small amount of information on federal student loans, a major area of interest of Tom Butts (the office's director from 1971-1977), is also included.
  - Coalition for Coordination of Student Financial Aid
    - 1976-1977, 2 folders (Box 8)
    - 1978-1979 (Box 8)
  - Department of Health, Education and Welfare Region V Evaluation 1974-1975 (Box 8)
  - Educator's Conference (sponsored by Congressmen Dingell and Ford) 1984-1994 (Box 8)
  - Governor's Commission on the Future of Higher Education 1984-1985 (Box 8)
  - Graduate Student Loan Program 1978-1980 (Box 9)
  - Higher Education Advisory Committee 1974-1976 (Box 9)
  - Michigan Higher Education Assistance Authority
    - Admissions Handbook 1981 (Box 9)
    - Competitive Scholarship 1979-1982 (Box 9)
    - Direct Loan Program 1975-1977 (Box 9)
    - Guaranteed Loan 1978-1981 (Box 9)
    - HR-11 Reports 1977-1986 (Box 9)
    - Legislative Merit 1978-1979 (Box 9)
    - Meeting 1976 (Box 9)
    - Tuition Differential Grant 1978-1979 (Box 9)
  - Michigan Postsecondary Admissions and Financial Assistance Handbook 1982-1983 (Box 9)
  - Michigan Student Financial Aid Association
    - General 1977-1985 (Box 9)
    - High School Counselor Workshops 1978 (Box 9)
    - Meetings 1976-1986 (Box 9)
    - Research Committee 1975-1978 (Box 9)
- Federal Funding Reports and Applications 1969-1993
  The Federal Funding Reports and Applications series, 1969-1993 (1 linear foot), is comprised mainly of applications, reports and supporting material for the Fiscal Operations Report and Application to Participate (FISAP), documentation which must be filed with the U.S. Department of Education each year in order for the university to receive federal funding for financial aid. The series also includes authorization and allocation notifications and separate applications for health professions funding.
  - Allocations 1970-1973 (Box 9)
  - Authorizations
    - 1973-1974 (Box 9)
    - 1975-1976 (Box 9)
  - Fiscal Operations Report and Application to Participate (FISAP)
    - 1969-1970 (Box 9)
    - 1970-1971 (Box 9)
    - 1971-1972 (Box 9)
    - 1972-1973 (Box 9)
    - 1973-1974 (Box 9)
    - 1974-1975 (Box 9)
    - 1975-1976 (Box 9)
    - 1976-1977 (Box 9)
    - 1977-1978 (Box 9)
    - 1978-1979 (Box 9)
    - 1979-1980 (Box 9)
    - 1980-1981 (Box 9)
    - 1981-1982 (Box 9)
    - 1982-1983 (Box 9)
    - Operating Report 1981-1982 and Application, 1983-1984 (Box 9)
    - Operating Report 1982-1983 and Application, 1984-1985 (Box 9)
    - Operating Report 1983-1984 and Application, 1985-1986 (Box 9)
    - Operating Report 1984-1985 and Application, 1986-1987 (Box 9)
    - Operating Report 1985-1986 and Application, 1987-1988 (Box 10)
    - Operating Report 1986-1987 and Application, 1988-1989 (Box 10)
    - Operating Report 1987-1988 and Application, 1989-1990 (Box 10)
    - Operating Report 1988-1989 and Application, 1990-1991 (Box 10)
    - Operating Report 1989-1990 and Application, 1991-1992 (Box 10)
    - Operating Report 1990-1991 and Application, 1992-1993 (Box 10)
  - Health Professions Applications 1977-1978 (Box 10)
  - Tri Parte Application 1972-1976 (Box 10)
- Alumni Scholarships 1954-2000
  The Alumni Scholarships series, 1954-2000 (1 linear foot), includes information on student scholarships and loan programs administered by the Alumni Association, as well as related initiatives. The administration of a number of these was transferred to the Office of Financial Aid in 1995, along with the staff position that oversaw the programs. The series includes summary information on individual named scholarships as well as larger scholarship programs. A small amount of information on recruitment efforts is also included in the series.
  - Alumnae Council 1965, 1991-1995 (Box 10)
  - Alumni Association Scholarship Programs 1992-2000 (Box 10)
  - Alumni Association Board of Directors' Student Support and Programs Committee
    - General 1991-1994 (Box 10)
    - Handbook 1991 (Box 10)
  - Alumni Fund Scholarships 1954-1955 (Box 10)
  - Alumni Merit Scholarship Coordinating Committee 1986 (Box 10)
  - Alumni Scholarship Programs-Dearborn and Flint Campuses 1991 (Box 10)
  - Ann Bloom/Elm Street Endowment Fund 1984 (Box 10)
  - Background Information 1972-1994 (Box 10)
  - Cook Family Foundation Gift 1985 (Box 10)
  - David J. Hallissey Scholarship 1985-1989 (Box 10)
  - Donald J. Ferguson Scholarship Fund 1976 (Box 10)
  - Frederick J. Vogt Student Aid Fund 1980-1983 (Box 10)
  - John R. James Alumni Loan 1984 (Box 10)
  - Loraine Gay Alumnae Council Scholarship Fund 1974-1975 (Box 10)
  - Malcolm Scholarship 1968-1973 (Box 10)
  - Margaret Ayers Host Fellowship 1984-1985 (Box 10)
  - Martin Luther King Scholars 1987-2000 (Box 10)
  - Martin Luther King Scholarship Fund Campaign 1995 (Box 10)
  - Michigan Annual Giving Scholars 1982-1995 (Box 10)
  - Mildred and Myron S. Steinberg Scholarship 1969 (Box 10)
  - Minority Recruitment 1984-1985 (Box 10)
  - Partee-Sanders Fund 1991 (Box 10)